bestfreewebresources.com 2018-10-11

# Privacy Policy - Free Web Resources

This privacy policy has been compiled to serve our users, who are concerned with how their data is used in our site. You have put your trust in us, and the data that we make available for you and hence, we also value your privacy. We, at Bestfreewebresources.com, take privacy issues seriously. We do use advertising from third party servers and we also collect user information. The following sections provide in details how Bestfreewebresources.com collects and uses the user information.

What personal information is collected from our website?

When you are visiting our site, we anonymously collect user information like location, traffic information and demographics. All these are collected anonymously and cannot be used to identify any user in particular.

We collect these information when you visit our site. No personal data is collected here. However, personal data is collected when you are signing up for our newsletter.

How do we use the information?

The information that is collected is mostly used to for making site improvements. The following are the uses of the collected user data.

  * We use the user data to personalize the website according to the usage of the website.
  * The user data is used to further streamline the website so as to serve you better.
  * We also use user data to provide better location specific services.

Our website is regularly scanned for security holes. All known vulnerabilities are patched as soon as they are detected. We value your privacy and hence your personal information is contained in secure networks with only selected people having access to them. A variety of security measures are implemented so that tampering with the user data can be avoided.

Yes, we use cookies on our website. Cookies are small files that is stored on your computer’s hard drive and can be accessed through the web browser if it is allowed by you. This allows us to retain certain information about the user, like your settings of the site, or preferences, based on your activity on our site.

We use cookies to understand the preferences of the user and provide him or her with more relevant content. We also use cookies for advertisements. Furthermore, cookies are used to compile aggregate data about site traffic that helps us to tune the website according to your needs. Sometimes, we may also use trusted third party cookies to track user activities on our behalf. You can disable cookies, but some related site features might be disabled tool.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit<http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

Our site may contain third party advertisements and these advertisements track your activities using cookies to provide relevant ads and increase advertising effectiveness. However, these do not have any relation with the content of our site and we are not responsible for how the advertising services will use the cookies. Furthermore there are also links to third party sites. We are not responsible or liable for any activity on those sites as they have their separate privacy polity. Nonetheless, we always try to maintain the integrity of our site are feedbacks are always welcome.
